<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Hackagong Teams &#8211; Hackagong</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/category/teams/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Regional Innovation Catalyst</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 03:23:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-AU</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.13</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Team Physics / Hackagong 2013</title>
		<link>/blog/team-physics-hackagong-2013/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 02:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hackagong]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Hackagong Teams]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hackagong.com/?p=715</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Team name Team Physics Team members Matt Sanderson, Luke Weynen, Matt Griffiths, Jackson Cunningham How did the team meet? All of team members are physicists, with Luke and Matt Griffiths studying at UoW, and Matt Sanderson and Jackson recently graduated from UoW. What did you build at Hackagong? We made an open-source, handheld gaming device,...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-physics-hackagong-2013/">Team Physics / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe width="848" height="477" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ush0uV1L5ZM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><strong>Team name</strong><br />
Team Physics</p>
<p><strong>Team members</strong><br />
Matt Sanderson, Luke Weynen, Matt Griffiths, Jackson Cunningham</p>
<p><strong>How did the team meet?</strong><br />
All of team members are physicists, with Luke and Matt Griffiths studying at UoW, and Matt Sanderson and Jackson recently graduated from UoW.</p>
<p><strong>What did you build at Hackagong?</strong><br />
We made an open-source, handheld gaming device, which we have called Pi.Py. The hardware consists of a modified Raspberry Pi connected to a 3.5” screen. This was all placed into a case created using the 3D printers available at Hackagong. We also wrote some software to interact with the games, and a version of pong based around special relativity.</p>
<p><strong>Why that idea and how did it come to you?</strong><br />
All of the team members are gamers, so we designed a product that we would consider buying. We also wanted to create something that could show off our wide range of skills, such as electronics, design, and coding.</p>
<p><strong>How was your weekend experience at Hackagong and/or Demo Day?</strong><br />
It was intense, almost everything that could go wrong did go wrong, and after 30 hours we were exhausted. But at the end of the day, the sense of achievement you get from creating a prototype in 30 hours can’t be beaten. All the other teams at Hackagong were amazing, and it was great to see so many fantastic ideas in one place.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s next for your product development?</strong><br />
We still have a few bugs to iron out, both in the code and hardware. It would also be nice to reprint the case, now that we have a better understanding of the possibilities and limitations of 3D printing.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s the grand future vision for what it could become?</strong><br />
It would be great if the device could be made cheap enough to be a viable contender in the marketplace. But if not, it would be great just to refine the design and get it out there so that other hackers can make their own and modify it in ways we can’t even imagine. The idea that anyone with the plans could print out their own handheld gaming device is quite exciting.</p>
<p><strong>Are you looking for people to help? If so, who/what do you need?</strong><br />
Investors are always welcome!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/IMG_5496-11.jpg"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-720" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/IMG_5496-11.jpg" alt="IMG_5496 (1)" /></a></p>
<p><a href="https://hackagong.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/MG_56571.jpg"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-547" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/MG_5657-1024x6821.jpg" alt="3D printed game controller" width="640" height="426" /></a></p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/pipy_menu1.png"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-717" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/pipy_menu1.png" alt="pipy_menu" /></a></p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/pipy_pong1.png"><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-719" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/pipy_pong1.png" alt="pipy_pong" width="640" height="481" /></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-physics-hackagong-2013/">Team Physics / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Team UOW FSAE / Hackagong 2013</title>
		<link>/blog/team-uow-fsae-hackagong-2013/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2013 23:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hackagong]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Hackagong Teams]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hackagong.com/?p=723</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Team name UOW FSAE Team members Samiyeul Habib How did the team meet? Part of UOW&#8217;s Formula-SAE team, a student based group that designs, engineers and builds a racecar each year. What did you build at Hackagong? A wearable rack for screwdriver bits, holds up to three different sizes of shanks. Always a nice accessory...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-uow-fsae-hackagong-2013/">Team UOW FSAE / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe width="848" height="477" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/biG1SJfLntA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><strong>Team name</strong><br />
<a href="http://www.uow-fsae.com/" target="_blank">UOW FSAE</a></p>
<p><strong>Team members</strong><br />
Samiyeul Habib</p>
<p><strong>How did the team meet?</strong><br />
Part of <a href="http://www.uow-fsae.com/" target="_blank">UOW&#8217;s Formula-SAE team</a>, a student based group that designs, engineers and builds a racecar each year.</p>
<p><strong>What did you build at Hackagong?</strong><br />
A wearable rack for screwdriver bits, holds up to three different sizes of shanks. Always a nice accessory bracelet for those with that in mind.</p>
<p><strong>How was your weekend experience at Hackagong and/or Demo Day?</strong><br />
It was pretty good, I had no complaints about anything. the weekend was organised very well, lots of food and drinks (as proven by the 12 Red Bulls I downed in that time haha). There was also great support from the organisers, especially Chris&#8217; help with my Build entry.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s next for your product development?</strong><br />
I plan to evolve and improve that design and look into selling copies of the actual thing on Shapeways. There was plenty of feedback from other teams and people about its practicality and aesthetics.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s the grand future vision for what it could become?</strong><br />
Nothing much really, it&#8217;s kinda becoming a part of my general portfolio of designs and things so it&#8217;s a win in its own way.</p>
<p><strong>Are you looking for people to help? If so, who/what do you need?</strong><br />
Not right now, I&#8217;ve already got people and friends that are willing to get behind the projects I have, just as a hobby. It&#8217;s more of a &#8220;you help me, i help you&#8221; kinda thing where we share ideas and plans.</p>
<p>Although I&#8217;d be interested in working with other Hackagongers, mainly because most of them have plans for their future and it could lead to some great collaboration. I consider myself skilled in CAD and graphics and things like that so there&#8217;s always a chance.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/uowfsae-Solidworks-Model1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-728" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/uowfsae-Solidworks-Model1.jpg" alt="uowfsae - Solidworks Model" width="640" height="318" /></a></p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/uowfsae-1st-Layer1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-724" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/uowfsae-1st-Layer1.jpg" alt="uowfsae - 1st Layer" width="960" height="720" /></a></p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/uowfsae-50-pct-and-5.5-hours1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-735" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/uowfsae-50-pct-and-5.5-hours1.jpg" alt="uowfsae - 50 pct and 5.5 hours" /></a></p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/uowfsae-100-pct-fresh-off-the-plate1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-734" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/uowfsae-100-pct-fresh-off-the-plate1.jpg" alt="uowfsae - 100 pct fresh off the plate" /></a></p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/uowfsae-100-pct-and-cleaned-up1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-737" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/uowfsae-100-pct-and-cleaned-up1.jpg" alt="uowfsae - 100 pct and cleaned up" /></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-uow-fsae-hackagong-2013/">Team UOW FSAE / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Team QUAD / Hackagong 2013</title>
		<link>/blog/team-quad-hackagong-2013/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 02:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hackagong]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Hackagong Teams]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hackagong.com/?p=739</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Team name QUAD Team members Nathan Roberts, Hannah Sloane, Jolie Nichols and Anton Summerfield How did the team meet? We all knew each other from uni or school. I (Nathan) approached Anton the week leading up to the event to see if he was interested and he jumped on without a second thought. Hannah joined...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-quad-hackagong-2013/">Team QUAD / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe width="848" height="477" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/syUdKrzT610?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><strong>Team name</strong><br />
QUAD</p>
<p><strong>Team members</strong><br />
Nathan Roberts, Hannah Sloane, Jolie Nichols and Anton Summerfield</p>
<p><strong>How did the team meet?</strong><br />
We all knew each other from uni or school. I (Nathan) approached Anton the week leading up to the event to see if he was interested and he jumped on without a second thought. Hannah joined up at the brewery and Jolie joined the Saturday morning.</p>
<p><strong>What did you build at Hackagong?</strong><br />
We designed and built using 3D printing a concept QUAD – Quadcopter Unified Aerofoil Design. The design fused the features of a quadcopter and a fixed wing aircraft.</p>
<p><strong>Why that idea and how did it come to you?</strong><br />
Quadcopters are very popular among professions and hobbyists alike due to their availability and flexibility. The biggest issue regarding the vast majority of users is its flight time. With the Hackagong event fast approaching and no solid ideas we were keen to come up with something innovative and ambitious. Over a coffee by the beach we were captivated by the seagull’s ability to harass people trying to enjoy hot chips with such little effort in flight. It was just the inspiration we needed. Why not give the quadcopter wings!</p>
<p><strong>How was your weekend experience at Hackagong and/or Demo Day?</strong><br />
Exceptional! What a way to spend the weekend, 30 hours of non-stop action! Having the opportunity to turn an idea into reality. Enthusiasm and passion was in the air with teams devoting themselves to projects that they came up with, that they were interested in, that they were skilled at. The venue at UOW was fantastic with plenty of space for teams to set up gear have a stretch and see what others were working on and plenty of bean bags for those needing a power nap. The Sunday where judges came around and the demo day was great in regards for teams to have an opportunity to pitch ideas and get feedback. Good experience.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s next for your product development?</strong><br />
Putting together a working model. To achieve this further calculations and considerations are required in the design. Pooling available resources, getting sponsors or people with suitable equipment together who are interested would accelerate the process significantly. Prototype aerofoil and quadcopter base structures may be produced using our 3D printer (that we won) with design iterations based on FEA, CFD, battery and flight data analysis.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s the grand future vision for what it could become?</strong><br />
To provide a platform to various users such as for high speed communications, real time monitoring of an area for disaster relief, search and rescue, farmers, wildlife surveys, police surveillance, weather and environmental monitoring and study. By incorporating sophisticated software into flight patterns and image analysis the uses are endless. Furthermore as 3D printing and material technologies improve the incorporation of conductive inks and polymers, solar cells, energy storage and artificial muscles will pave the way for a superior platform for professionals and everyday users.</p>
<p><strong>Are you looking for people to help? If so, who/what do you need?</strong><br />
Anyone may help contribute to advancing QUAD from programmers, computer scientist and engineers to people interested in just wanting to have fun and fly around with a quadcopter. Key areas will be sensory input, and utilising control theory to help control flight. If people own a quadcopter or have components they wish to incorporate into the frame then that would be of great help. Anyone interested are valuable.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://hackagong.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/quad1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-743" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/quad-1024x5751.jpg" alt="quad" width="640" height="359" /></a></p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/IMG_56291.jpg"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-741" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/IMG_56291.jpg" alt="IMG_5629" /></a></p>
<p><a href="https://hackagong.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/IMG_562811.jpg"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-570" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/IMG_56281-1024x6821.jpg" alt="More 3D printing" width="640" height="426" /></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-quad-hackagong-2013/">Team QUAD / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Team Enactus / Hackagong 2013</title>
		<link>/blog/team-enactus-hackagong-2013/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 02:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hackagong]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Hackagong Teams]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hackagong.com/?p=712</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Team name Enactus Wollongong Team members Marc Bowditch &#38; Eric Perry How did the team meet? Through the UOW Enactus Club. What did you build at Hackagong? We fixed up the Enactus website and CSE Enactus website. Why that idea and how did it come to you? Our website needed updating. How was your weekend...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-enactus-hackagong-2013/">Team Enactus / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe width="848" height="477" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RhONup57V_U?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><strong>Team name</strong><br />
Enactus Wollongong</p>
<p><strong>Team members</strong><br />
Marc Bowditch &amp; Eric Perry</p>
<p><strong>How did the team meet?</strong><br />
Through the <a href="http://enactusuow.org/" target="_blank">UOW Enactus Club</a>.</p>
<p><strong>What did you build at Hackagong?</strong><br />
We fixed up the Enactus website and CSE Enactus website.</p>
<p><strong>Why that idea and how did it come to you?</strong><br />
Our website needed updating.</p>
<p><strong>How was your weekend experience at Hackagong and/or Demo Day?</strong><br />
We had an amazing time, we meet so many people doing interesting projects.</p>
<p><strong>Are you looking for people to help? If so, who/what do you need?</strong><br />
If you want to join Enactus you can find more information here: http://clubs.uow.edu.au/clubs/enactus/home/</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-enactus-hackagong-2013/">Team Enactus / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Team Repair My Road / Hackagong 2013</title>
		<link>/blog/team-repair-my-road-hackagong-2013/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2013 08:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hackagong]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Hackagong Teams]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hackagong.com/?p=797</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Team name Repair My Road Team members Danny Henley-Martin, Andrew Booth, Trung Nguyen, Kaegyn Toole, Diego Biancullo How did the team meet? Not everyone knew each other, some of us met at uni, while some met at work and we just asked if discussed if we wanted to do something at Hackagong. What did you...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-repair-my-road-hackagong-2013/">Team Repair My Road / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe width="848" height="477" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/EMS0C-eG58U?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><strong>Team name</strong><br />
Repair My Road</p>
<p><strong>Team members</strong><br />
Danny Henley-Martin, Andrew Booth, Trung Nguyen, Kaegyn Toole, Diego Biancullo</p>
<p><strong>How did the team meet?</strong><br />
Not everyone knew each other, some of us met at uni, while some met at work and we just asked if discussed if we wanted to do something at Hackagong.</p>
<p><strong>What did you build at Hackagong?</strong><br />
We built a mobile application that collects reports from users about potholes that they have discovered while driving. The app then sent this data to a server that filters the results to be displayed and used by governments to repair the potholes that have been reported.</p>
<p><strong>Why that idea and how did it come to you?</strong><br />
Basically, we wanted to go to Hackagong for the experience. But the idea came to a couple of us while we were driving to Hungry Jacks one day when we were taking a break from study. On the way, we saw a few potholes on the Freeway. Haha, it was pretty funny actually because, we said to ourselves, that &#8220;this could be an app&#8221;, and so we moved forward with that idea.</p>
<p><strong>How was your weekend experience at Hackagong and/or Demo Day?</strong><br />
Our experience at Hackagong was quite good actually, for us, we were learning how to build our app, while creating it on the day, so it was a great experience. One of the best things was just to be in an environment that supported the development of our ideas, and having other people around you working towards something is always a great motivator. Hackagong was probably the best thing to happen for us as a group, and we&#8217;ll be sure to go again to the next one. Demo Day was even better, because this is where we were able to present our idea to a crowd of people, find and gain interest, while receiving important feedback about our app, and how we could move forward with it. Making it into the top 10 was crucial for us, because Demo Day would be our platform to push our idea.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s next for your product development?</strong><br />
At the moment, we are expanding on our initial app, and building it towards how the government can use the data from the application to make better, quicker and more strategic decisions when it comes to civil works and maintenance on our local and state roads. A big factor is our user-interface development, and how users will interact with the &#8220;dashboard&#8221;, as well as the mobile application. We&#8217;re hoping to pitch the idea to governments soon.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s the grand future vision for what it could become?</strong><br />
We are hoping to see our app used by States, and local governments, where citizens as the primary users can report seen potholes, quickly and easily. We also want to provide citizens with some other useful utilities while driving, such as recording journey distance for tax purposes, displaying their current speed, as well as showing traffic congestion around their driving area. We have a couple other things up our sleeves too, but for now they are under wraps.</p>
<p><strong>Are you looking for people to help? If so, who/what do you need?</strong><br />
We may need people in the future, but for the time been we have a fairly good robust team. Anything we require in the future, would be security based, and to provide us with strategic overview of how this could integrate into existing services.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s happened with the project since Hackagong?</strong><br />
Since Hackagong, we have been approached by several enthusiastic people that are keen to get on board and help out by providing us with contacts in the government and people that want to be application testers. For us, we&#8217;ve continued to work to refine our app and push it further, greatly expanding our analytics user-interface for the government and finding new ways for our data to be useful. But most of all, we&#8217;re finding new ways to make the app fun for the everyday citizen and incentivise its use.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/04-tag-slide1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-801" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/04-tag-slide1.jpg" alt="04 tag slide" width="1920" height="1200" /></a></p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/03-cam-slide1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-800" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/03-cam-slide1.jpg" alt="03 cam slide" width="1920" height="1200" /></a></p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/02-quick-slide1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-799" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/02-quick-slide1.jpg" alt="02 quick slide" width="1920" height="1200" /></a></p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/09-admin-maps1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-804" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/09-admin-maps1.jpg" alt="09 admin-maps" width="1920" height="1200" /></a></p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/07-admin-priority1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-803" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/07-admin-priority1.jpg" alt="07 admin-priority" width="1920" height="1200" /></a></p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/06-admin-dash1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-802" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/06-admin-dash1.jpg" alt="06 admin-dash" width="1920" height="1200" /></a></p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/Tableview1.png"><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-798" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/Tableview1.png" alt="Tableview" width="1667" height="723" /></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-repair-my-road-hackagong-2013/">Team Repair My Road / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Team Whiteboard / Hackagong 2013</title>
		<link>/blog/team-whiteboard-hackagong-2013/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 00:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hackagong]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Hackagong Teams]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hackagong.com/?p=709</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Team name Team Whiteboard Team members Andrew Short, Neil Richardson, Simon Westren How did the team meet? We met at Hackagong for the first time. What did you build at Hackagong? We built a robotic whiteboard that lets you choose an image and have it drawn on a whiteboard. Why that idea and how did...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-whiteboard-hackagong-2013/">Team Whiteboard / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe width="848" height="477" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/4TZ8R8GbxuM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><strong>Team name</strong><br />
Team Whiteboard</p>
<p><strong>Team members</strong><br />
Andrew Short, Neil Richardson, Simon Westren</p>
<p><strong>How did the team meet?</strong><br />
We met at Hackagong for the first time.</p>
<p><strong>What did you build at Hackagong?</strong><br />
We built a robotic whiteboard that lets you choose an image and have it drawn on a whiteboard.</p>
<p><strong>Why that idea and how did it come to you?</strong><br />
We had a few components and this was one idea which fitted the hardware we had available.</p>
<p><strong>How was your weekend experience at Hackagong and/or Demo Day?</strong><br />
It was a whole lot of fun, and was great to work on an interesting project in such an exciting atmosphere.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s next for your product development?</strong><br />
It was more of a fun project than a product, but there may be a version 2 being made in the future.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s the grand future vision for what it could become?</strong><br />
A really cool demo.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s happened with the project since Hackagong?</strong><br />
While we had a successful presentation at Demo-Day, the technological constraints mentioned above have meant that little has happened since then.</p>
<p><a href="https://hackagong.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/IMG_570011.jpg"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-571" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/IMG_57001-1024x6821.jpg" alt="Robotic whiteboard that draws whatever you program it to" width="640" height="426" /></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-whiteboard-hackagong-2013/">Team Whiteboard / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Team Flush Arcade / Hackagong 2013</title>
		<link>/blog/team-flush-arcade-hackagong-2013/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 10:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hackagong]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Hackagong Teams]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hackagong.com/?p=745</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Team name Flush Arcade Team members Michael Williams What did you build at Hackagong? App Name &#8211; Fanatic Mobile App for helping artists push content to their fans. the idea behind the application is to drive fans to obtain a place within an artist&#8217;s top fans list meaning prizes for fans who make it within...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-flush-arcade-hackagong-2013/">Team Flush Arcade / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Team name</strong><br />
Flush Arcade</p>
<p><strong>Team members</strong><br />
Michael Williams</p>
<p><strong>What did you build at Hackagong?</strong><br />
App Name &#8211; Fanatic</p>
<p>Mobile App for helping artists push content to their fans. the idea behind the application is to drive fans to obtain a place within an artist&#8217;s top fans list meaning prizes for fans who make it within the artists top fan&#8217;s list. Artists post any sort of content through their profile and fans have the ability to share this information in order to build points and climb ranks within each artist&#8217;s top friends list. The application also allows artists to start chat rooms where fans can ask them questions directly.</p>
<p><strong>Why that idea and how did it come to you?</strong><br />
I run a record label and deal with artists all the time looking for ways to push content to their fans, all artists want the most efficient way to achieve this.</p>
<p><strong>How was your weekend experience at Hackagong and/or Demo Day?</strong><br />
Exhausting but well worth it. It was a very enjoyable experience being involved in the creative atmosphere and highly interesting seeing what products each team comes up with.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s next for your product development?</strong><br />
Aiming to have a further developed product and test out with some of the artists on my record label.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s the grand future vision for what it could become?</strong><br />
To become a highly used social media platform for all artists on any smartphone. I think one of the biggest aims would be to get some big artists from labels such as Sony or Universal on board with it.</p>
<p><strong>Are you looking for people to help? If so, who/what do you need?</strong><br />
At the moment no but depending on how it starts look for the future after testing the first pro type with some of the artists thats when I will look into building it into something much bigger.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-flush-arcade-hackagong-2013/">Team Flush Arcade / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Team Lime Rocket (Epic Games) / Hackagong 2013</title>
		<link>/blog/team-lime-rocket-epic-games-hackagong-2013/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 09:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hackagong]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Hackagong Teams]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hackagong.com/?p=754</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Team name Lime Rocket Team members Mike Gardiner &#38; Gretchen Armitage How did the team meet? We came in as a company team representing Lime Rocket &#8211; an game &#38; app development company based right here in the Illawarra. What did you build at Hackagong? Using our Buzzy.IO platform we built the first of a...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-lime-rocket-epic-games-hackagong-2013/">Team Lime Rocket (Epic Games) / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe width="848" height="477" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8XZhWJoETPk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><strong>Team name</strong><br />
<a href="http://limerocket.com/" target="_blank">Lime Rocket</a></p>
<p><strong>Team members</strong><br />
Mike Gardiner &amp; Gretchen Armitage</p>
<p><strong>How did the team meet?</strong><br />
We came in as a company team representing <a href="http://limerocket.com/" target="_blank">Lime Rocket</a> &#8211; an game &amp; app development company based right here in the Illawarra.</p>
<p><strong>What did you build at Hackagong?</strong><br />
Using our <a href="http://buzzy.io/" target="_blank">Buzzy.IO</a> platform we built the first of a new series of Epic multi-screen games for pubs &amp; clubs that allow patrons to play via your iOS or Android SmartPhone.</p>
<p><strong>Why that idea and how did it come to you?</strong><br />
Hackagong for us was an opportunity to eat our own dog food (API &amp; SDK) and show other game &amp; app developers what is possible using Buzzy.IO. The idea started out early Saturday as location based dating and by mid morning it had morphed into game shows.</p>
<p><strong>How was your weekend experience at Hackagong and/or Demo Day?</strong><br />
Intense. Fun. Epic. What&#8217;s not to love?</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s next for your product development?</strong><br />
We are continuing to develop &amp; refine more games and signup new venues. At the EB Games Expo (Oct 4-6) we will be showcasing these games to the 30,000+ gamers that will visit over the 3 days.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s the grand future vision for what it could become?</strong><br />
Our aim is to use your SmartPhone, Buzzy.IO &amp; games like Epic to enable a new world of social gaming.</p>
<p><strong>Are you looking for people to help? If so, who/what do you need?</strong><br />
We are currently looking for rockstar developers (TypeScript, JS, ActionScript, C#) and designers who have an interest in mobile or social games and want to build amazing tools &amp; content. Devs<br />
&amp; designers can reach out to us on twitter via <a href="http://twitter.com/LimeRocketApps" target="_blank">@LimeRocketApps</a>, <a href="http://www.linkedin.com/company/lime-rocket/" target="_blank">LinkedIN</a>, or our <a href="http://facebook.com/LimeRocket" target="_blank">Facebook Page</a>.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s happened with the project since Hackagong?</strong><br />
We are now running the Epic interactive games weekly at our flagship venue The Illawarra Brewery and have several others waiting to come online soon.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://hackagong.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/epic-brewery-limerocket1.png"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-755" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/epic-brewery-limerocket-1024x6261.png" alt="epic-brewery-limerocket" width="640" height="391" /></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-lime-rocket-epic-games-hackagong-2013/">Team Lime Rocket (Epic Games) / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Team Arts Eclectic / Hackagong 2013</title>
		<link>/blog/team-arts-eclectic-hackagong-2013/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2013 07:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hackagong]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Hackagong Teams]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hackagong.com/?p=697</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Team name Arts Eclectic Team members Stephen Mason, Sophia Dichomides, Fox Lee, Talen Lee, Geoff Murphy How did the team meet? Most of the team has known one another for years. But we did meet Geoff a few nights before the event at a Hackagong meetup. What did you build at Hackagong? At Hackagong we...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-arts-eclectic-hackagong-2013/">Team Arts Eclectic / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe width="848" height="477" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/PZ9eb96HmB4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><iframe width="848" height="636" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/p2UJ18d3QNM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><strong>Team name</strong><br />
<a href="http://arts-eclectic.com/" target="_blank">Arts Eclectic</a></p>
<p><strong>Team members</strong><br />
Stephen Mason, Sophia Dichomides, Fox Lee, Talen Lee, Geoff Murphy</p>
<p><strong>How did the team meet?</strong><br />
Most of the team has known one another for years. But we did meet Geoff a few nights before the event at a Hackagong meetup.</p>
<p><strong>What did you build at Hackagong?</strong><br />
At Hackagong we built the prototype for a 3D printable boardgame, called &#8216;Riggers&#8217;.</p>
<p><strong>Why that idea and how did it come to you?</strong><br />
We pretty much came up with it on the day, in response to needing an idea that both appealed to us (boardgames) and used new technology (3D printers).</p>
<p><strong>How was your weekend experience at Hackagong and/or Demo Day?</strong><br />
Pretty good, exciting and fun. It really showed us what we could achieve if we put our minds to it. (it was dam cold though :p)</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s next for your product development?</strong><br />
The product is currently on the shelf until 3D printing technology catches up.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s the grand future vision for what it could become?</strong><br />
One of our group members is currently starting a table-top gaming business of his own, and, it is possible that, one day, &#8216;Riggers&#8217; could become part of that business&#8217;s product range and people around the world could be playing it.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s happened with the project since Hackagong?</strong><br />
While we had a successful presentation at Demo-Day, the technological constraints mentioned above have meant that little has happened since then.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/Riggers-Photo-Closed1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-703" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/Riggers-Photo-Closed1.jpg" alt="Riggers Photo Closed" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/Riggers-Closed1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-702" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/Riggers-Closed1.jpg" alt="Riggers Closed" width="640" height="480" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/Riggers-Open1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-701" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/Riggers-Open1.jpg" alt="Riggers Open" width="640" height="480" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/Riggers-Photo-Half-Open1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-700" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/Riggers-Photo-Half-Open1.jpg" alt="Riggers Photo Half Open" width="640" height="433" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://hackagong.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/Riggers-Photo-Open1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-699" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/Riggers-Photo-Open-1024x5531.jpg" alt="Riggers Photo Open" width="640" height="345" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-arts-eclectic-hackagong-2013/">Team Arts Eclectic / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Team CoLab / Hackagong 2013</title>
		<link>/blog/team-colab-hackagong-2013/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 03:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hackagong]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Hackagong Teams]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hackagong.com/?p=682</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Team name CoLab Team members Jody Watts, Chris Reid, Tim Randall How did the team meet? At the Hackabar meet up the Thursday night before Hackagong! What did you build at Hackagong? We built CoLab – A website to facilitate the connection of people looking for projects and startups looking for skills Why that idea...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-colab-hackagong-2013/">Team CoLab / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe width="848" height="477" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yp74t0PGPbo?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p><strong>Team name</strong><br />
CoLab</p>
<p><strong>Team members</strong><br />
Jody Watts, Chris Reid, Tim Randall</p>
<p><strong>How did the team meet?</strong><br />
At the Hackabar meet up the Thursday night before Hackagong!</p>
<p><strong>What did you build at Hackagong?</strong><br />
We built CoLab – A website to facilitate the connection of people looking for projects and startups looking for skills</p>
<p><strong>Why that idea and how did it come to you?</strong><br />
Tim was finding it hard to fill the skills gaps in his project ideas and asked a question. Why isn&#8217;t there a register of all the awesome people who are keen to work on new things improve their skills and have the chance of starting a successful company or change the local community for the better? Also information on local projects and startups is fragmented, how do all the people in Wollongong and UOW who want to work with startups find them? We created CoLab to solve this.</p>
<p><strong>How was your weekend experience at Hackagong and/or Demo Day?</strong><br />
It was amazing because of the short period things happen fast, decisions have to be made quick! There was no time to waste.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s next for your product development?</strong><br />
Hopefully $5000 from <a href="http://www.uow.edu.au/research/icr/events/UOW150491.html" target="_blank">UOW Pitch</a> and a minimum viable product completed in December.</p>
<p><strong>What&#8217;s the grand future vision for what it could become?</strong><br />
An extremely valuable tool for people who want to start companies by connecting like minded people with different skill sets, speeding up innovation and economic development in communities. The information hub for every startup community in every city on Earth and not just the startup community, a tool to help any interested person connect to projects/companies they are interested in.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/colab-mobile1.png"><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-690" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/colab-mobile1.png" alt="colab-mobile" width="468" height="331" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/colab-community1.jpg"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-687" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/colab-community1.jpg" alt="colab-community" width="640" height="962" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/team-colab-hackagong-2013/">Team CoLab / Hackagong 2013</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.w3-edge.com/products/

Object Caching 71/229 objects using disk
Page Caching using disk: enhanced 

Served from: www.hackagong.com @ 2020-02-03 15:59:49 by W3 Total Cache
-->