<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Thoughts &#8211; Hackagong</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/category/thoughts/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Regional Innovation Catalyst</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 03:23:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-AU</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.13</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Hackagong Guide to Building Your Team</title>
		<link>/blog/the-hackagong-guide-to-building-your-team/</link>
		<comments>/blog/the-hackagong-guide-to-building-your-team/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 22:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hackagong]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Thoughts]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hackagong.com/?p=353</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>There are few things more exhilarating than turning your own ideas into manifested realities. Making something new that has never existed before, and as a bonus, finding a group of people somewhere in the world who absolutely love your creation is what Hackagong is all about. But how do we go about achieving this kind...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/the-hackagong-guide-to-building-your-team/">The Hackagong Guide to Building Your Team</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/teamwork1.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-large wp-image-363" src="https://159.203.208.10/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/teamwork-1024x6831.jpg" alt="teamwork" width="640" height="426" /></a></p>
<p>There are few things more exhilarating than turning your own ideas into manifested realities. Making something new that has never existed before, and as a bonus, finding a group of people somewhere in the world who absolutely love your creation is what Hackagong is all about. But how do we go about achieving this kind of glorious success? What kind of team do we need to assemble at Hackagong to make all this happen?</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s what a few people involved in last years Hackagong had to say about building a strong team:</p>
<p><em>&#8220;In my opinion the perfect Hackagong team would be three or four people: a business/marketer/speaker/people person, a designer/UI/UX/graphics person, and one or two programmer/engineer/architect people. It&#8217;s good to have people who&#8217;s strengths are in those specific areas, but the more team members have overlapping skills, the more adaptive and cohesive they will be.&#8221;</em></p>
<p>Nathan Waters</p>
<p><em>&#8220;It&#8217;s important for people to realise that 2 front end programmers / 2 back end developers is not a perfectly balanced team (like I naively thought it was) &#8211; I&#8217;d say every team should really look for a creative person (e.g. graphic designer) if possible. That&#8217;s what made the winning teams last year stand out.&#8221;</em></p>
<p>Tim Christie</p>
<p><em>&#8220;Put together a team with a range of skills that can be put into many different types of projects. Designers &amp; Entrepreneurs I would say are the most valuable, as they can work on almost any project.&#8221;</em></p>
<p>Brennan Hatton</p>
<p><em>&#8220;A balanced team, in my view, needs 2 people: 1 dev and 1 business. Designers and other skills can be bought in later. Having a designer can really help. As Tim said, they can help to make what you have made look good!!&#8221;</em></p>
<p>Rebecca Paget</p>
<p>What other hints can we take from last year to help us figure out what makes a solid Hackagong team? Hackagong 2012 winners Giftling was a team of four, consisting of <b>one graphic designer</b>, <b>one software developer</b>, <b>one business development person</b> and <b>one person that could do a little of everything</b>.</p>
<p>It seems good Hackagong team is all about striking a <b>well-rounded balance of people who have different knowledge and skill sets</b>. Teams need to be able to build stuff, from graphics to code to models to marketing plans, <b>well</b> and <b>fast</b>. This means you need people who are really good at a particular thing, but are knowledgeable enough in other things to be able to work cohesively with others and function as a team.</p>
<p>The judges will be looking for a combination of lots of things, so you&#8217;ve got to have a team that can cover them &#8211; your creation <b>has to work, </b>it needs to be<b> comfortable to look at and use, </b>be underpinned by an awesome <b>innovative idea</b>, and have <b>potential for future development</b> as a product that will resonate with a wide audience (well outside the hacker community). Lots of things to worry about, so you&#8217;ve got to have a well-rounded team of hands on deck to be able to cover them all <b>properly</b>.</p>
<p>How is your Hackagong team looking? Do you have that balance?</p>
<p>If you don&#8217;t have it and need help finding people to balance out your team, checkout the <a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/hackagongers/" target="_blank">HACKAGONGers facebook group</a> where competitors are posting their skills or get in contact with our Hackagong ambassadors to help match you up with somebody from their field:</p>
<p>Travis Wall &#8211; <em>Design</em> &#8211; <a href="mailto:travis@hackagong.com">travis@hackagong.com</a></p>
<p>Tim Christie &#8211; <em>Code</em> &#8211; <a href="mailto:tim@hackagong.com">tim@hackagong.com</a></p>
<p>Chris Richards &#8211; <em>Build</em> &#8211; <a href="mailto:chris@hackagong.com">chris@hackagong.com</a></p>
<p>Rebecca Paget &#8211; <em>Launch</em> &#8211; <a href="mailto:bec@hackagong.com">bec@hackagong.com</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/the-hackagong-guide-to-building-your-team/">The Hackagong Guide to Building Your Team</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/the-hackagong-guide-to-building-your-team/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>HACKAGONG: The Beginnings</title>
		<link>/blog/hackagong-the-beginnings/</link>
		<comments>/blog/hackagong-the-beginnings/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 06:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hackagong]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Thoughts]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hackagong.com/?p=143</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>HACKAGONG began very much like a lean startup, with very humble beginnings. Myself and business partner, Tristan Grace, had just come back from the Sensis API Hackathon (SAPIhack) held in March 2012 at Pollenizer in Surry Hills, Sydney. It was the first hackathon we&#8217;d ever attended, and was an incredibly awesome experience. We met some...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/hackagong-the-beginnings/">HACKAGONG: The Beginnings</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HACKAGONG began very much like a lean startup, with very humble beginnings.</p>
<p>Myself and business partner, Tristan Grace, had just come back from the <a href="http://developers.sensis.com.au/blog/read/Sydney_Hackathon">Sensis API Hackathon</a> (SAPIhack) held in March 2012 at <a href="http://pollenizer.com/">Pollenizer</a> in Surry Hills, Sydney. It was the first hackathon we&#8217;d ever attended, and was an incredibly awesome experience. We met some very talented people, including some big names in the Sydney startup scene. Our creation, called &#8220;Yellow Fridge&#8221;, was an attempt to make a more social Yellow Pages ranked by social data and what your friends liked. After being exposed for the first time (of many) to Pollenizer co-founder, Mick Liubinskas&#8217; famous talk on &#8220;<a href="http://vimeo.com/38493795">Focus</a>&#8220;, we decided to focus on restaurant searches only. So if you searched for &#8220;italian&#8221; in &#8220;Surry Hills&#8221; it would search the Yellow Pages results, and also search and combine Facebook pages and checkins, ordering the results by most popular.</p>
<p>Anyway, we didn&#8217;t take home the overall winner, but we won a cash prize and Pollenizer took such a liking to our solution and the audacity of our <a href="http://42startups.com/">42startups</a> initiative (building a new startup per week), that they offered us desk space and mentoring at Pollenizer for 4 months!</p>
<p>At this stage we were in <a href="http://startpad.com.au/">StartPad</a>, an incubator in Wollongong that is run by the university. And as soon as we got back, we mentioned to the StartPad management that Wollongong definitely needed its own hackathon. I felt that in just one weekend, we&#8217;d learned quite a lot about how to launch a startup and what to be focusing on (customers!), and this was something the fledgling Wollongong startup scene really needed.</p>
<p>Fast forward a few months to October 2012, and nothing had happened. I&#8217;d just finished building a website that used the <a href="http://angel.co/">AngelList</a> API to showcase <a href="http://gongstartups.com/">Wollongong startups</a>, and so the local spirit was flowing.</p>
<p>We&#8217;d been in StartPad since the beginning of the year and I was clashing with their motivations and management style at the time, so we knew we probably wouldn&#8217;t get back in the next year.</p>
<p>So I thought, &#8220;screw it, I&#8217;ll try this myself&#8221;  and just see if anyone wanted a Wollongong hackathon. I put up a simple Facebook event asking &#8220;Any interest in a Wollongong hackathon?&#8221; and within two weeks, about 80 people had RSVP&#8217;d with either a yes or maybe.</p>
<p>I then pitched the idea at the next eClub where I found a bunch of very cool people who were willing to help organise.</p>
<p>And as they say, the rest is history.</p>
<p>Though even with a posse of talented volunteer organisers, actually organising the first event was very difficult, often consisting of 12-15 hour days, 7 days per week. There were issues with venues, issues with people wanting to stop it from happening altogether, issues with bureaucracies, issues with time, and of course the stress of the unknown: would we find enough sponsorship to cover costs and prizes?, would enough people turn up? etc.</p>
<p>Amazingly, all of it came together in less than 8 weeks from when I first put up the Facebook event asking for interest. I&#8217;ve never organised an event this large before, and never had to raise sponsorship before. For the inaugural event we had 90 competitors across 27 teams and raised a total of $20,000. There were hiccups, but the feedback from everyone was overwhelmingly positive, and now we have a brand and a cool event that we can grow together as a community to help rapidly bring about a vibrant startup and hacker culture in Wollongong.</p>
<p>So I would say to anyone out there, if you want to do something, just fucking do it and don&#8217;t let anything get in the way.</p>
<p>Cheers, <a href="http://nathanwaters.com/">Nathan Waters</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog/hackagong-the-beginnings/">HACKAGONG: The Beginnings</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hackagong</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/hackagong-the-beginnings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.w3-edge.com/products/

Object Caching 32/63 objects using disk
Page Caching using disk: enhanced 

Served from: www.hackagong.com @ 2020-02-03 15:59:52 by W3 Total Cache
-->